I'm on a journey out to see
the world While I'm on my own,
I've yet to reach the end So won't
you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea
For that treasure known
by everybody as One Piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon.
The rain will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the anchor.
Now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm.
The storm that you have built within.
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up.
We set stuff cause we can't.
Thresh enough, stand tall.
And take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me want to see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story most will believe.
Not me, come and see.
I am on a journey out to see.
The world done on my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
All aboard!
Huh? Hey, look!
It's the princess!
Princess Vivi!
We love you!
Did you notice that?
Didn't Vivi seem eager to go, Koza?
I guess it's because she's
feeling like a pirate again,
and here I thought she
was becoming more refined.
Yes, Hina speaking, we just left Alabasta.
I'm headed to Mariegeois as we speak,
I'm traveling with the Nefertari family.
Captain Hina, I got you flowers.
I personally handpicked these for you.
Throw them away, now, full body,
Django, return to your positions!
Ma 'am.
Be careful, I beg you!
That's far too dangerous.
Princess Phoebe.
Come down from there!
Before something terrible happens.
Princess, please.
The ocean breeze is so refreshing.
You must be careful.
What if a gargantuan fowl
were to snatch you away?
Or worse yet, if a sniper
has his sights on you.
A stray meteorite could
also plummet upon you.
You're being such a worrywart.
Princess Vivi was once a pirate.
Have you lost your mind?
The Navy's watching all around us.
Don't push yourself, Your Majesty.
If you're indisposed, we can
turn the fleet around at once.
No, I'll be fine.
Ever since the day I met Nico Robin,
I've had some questions for the
world government I'd like answered.
All I wanted was to
learn our true history.
And to share it with the whole world.
Are you referring to the Poneglyphs, sir?
Precisely why I am determined
to attend this year's referee.
And if it's at all possible,
I would like to discover what the Nefertari
lineage did to the world many years ago.
No!
Oh, no, no!
Oh, goodness, no!
Hey, enough misbehavior, Princess Meavy!
How are you feeling, my dear father.
Honestly, not well.
I may not have much time left.
If only my daughter would
marry before I pass.
There you go again,
using your illness to try and guilt me
into marriage—we have piles of pictures!
pictures of potential suitors, though.
You can toss them out.
Congratulations on your enthronement, sir.
Our hotel prides itself.
On being built exclusively
for housing nobles.
who attend the reverie every four years.
We do hope you enjoy your stay with us.
It isn't bad, but it isn't isn't bad.
Isn't that right, dear?
It's rather pedestrian.
Its only unique trait is that it offers
a view of Gold Roger's execution stand.
I'm sure you're fatigued after your
long journey here, King Stella.
True.
Now be gone from my room,
you unsightly trash.
Yes, sir!
All countries of the
world are currently abuzz
due to an event that happens
once every four years.
In the holy land of Marie
Joie called the reverie,
here at this elite conference leaders
of 50 nations will gather together.
In order to debate and negotiate matters
of concern from all over the world.
setting a course for the future.
However,
these larger-than-life leaders
can prove crafty and conniving,
so they often fail to see
eye-to-eye, to say the least.
The leader of the Haposui army,
Don Chin Zhao, forgive me, I mean
Don Sai, has yet to return, correct?
Ever since Straw Hat and his allies
took down the Doflamingo family,
Our enemy has been unable
to acquire additional arms.
Thanks to that, the war is now over.
It seems like we can make
it to the reverie after all.
There is quite a bit I'd like
to get off my chest this time.
I cannot go!
I'm scared!
Besides, Luffy made a promise to me.
The next time we get to meet in person,
he's taking me on a walk in
a real forest on the surface.
Yes, of course.
I'm certain that Luffy will make good
on his word and take you all about.
But I'm afraid for this
particular trip that
she'll only be directly
upwards to Marie Joie.
Your brothers, as well as the Neptune
army, will gladly escort you, Princess.
Just...
now, now, dear one.
Father, perhaps she should remain
here while we all go. Latino!
We've already wielded in
a ton of signatures on
the petition to migrate to
Fishman Island after all.
Mambo!
It's not as simple as that. If she stays,
I fear that our actions
may indicate to the
humans that we don't entirely trust them,
Jamon.
What should we do?
Shirahoshi, didn't you learn
anything from the Straw Hat crew?
This forthcoming meeting was the
greatest desire of our mother.
Please join us.
King Wapol, bad news!
The drum kingdom you
once ruled over is now
calling themselves the
Cherry Blossom Kingdom.
It appears Dalton will be attending
the reverie as their king.
What?
That's a stupid name for a kingdom.
Curse you, Dalton!
Very well.
I'll have to put him in
his place at the reverie.
What?
You can't be serious, Dr. Karoo.
This is all a joke, right?
Oh, don't look so disappointed, Dalton.
You wouldn't travel
without a doctor, right?
That's where I come in.
Ain't you happy?
You'd really take me?
I'd love to.
Though you'd serve as my attendant, okay?
Yeah? Really? Why?
Thanks so much!
That's so exciting, Rebecca! Right?
You can have whichever gown you like.
Oh, but... Huh?
Well, what if I chose one my mom wore?
That sounds lovely to me.
King Rick, I turned down
that naval fleet escort.
I think we should travel together.
Hmm, Elisabello, it's not a holiday.
Come on, loosen up a little.
The river is just a big party to me.
Meanwhile, Luffy's group
faces their own struggles.
Turn it starboard.
Okay, so this way?
No, chopper, that way.
Pull it together!
Come on, every water do you wanna sink?
Shut up, Luffy!
That big plunge from the
elephant wore us out!
Now we're all suffering from trauma!
You have my gratitude.
Having nearly lost my life, you taught me.
To savor what I've got, on the
flip side, I'll murder you.
Oh, no.
We swerved a bit off course just now.
Turn to port, if you can.
Okay!
Leave it to me! Look at her!
She's perfectly fine! Do you have...
Wow, we're really in the water, huh?
This thing looks ultra-heavy, but
it's colliding like it's in the air.
What are you doing on the ship?
Carrots here?
Carrot?
But why?
I decided to tag along.
Got you!
Nabi!
Mach!
Chopper!
Baron corpse!
Too bony!
I'm sorry, but we must take Yugara back.
Please don't!
Wada's gonna be so mad at me!
So, Yugara would rather be
a nuisance to our saviors?
If I wanted to go on an adventure
with everyone just once in my life,
I didn't mean any harm!
We're infiltrating the lair of an Emperor.
This is no game!
Pedro!
Take me with you, Tia!
I swear I won't cause any trouble!
I came prepared!
I brought lunch, juice,
a snack, and... a shirt!
Were you Russians last you?
I'd say a good half day!
The sea's pretty big, isn't it?
Did you mean to take several
days to reach the island?
Even going straight there?
How can anything be so enormous?
The ocean truly is a wonderland.
This will be my first sleepover.
It's not a wonderland.
There's no land to speak of.
Well, you're on board now, so
we'll just have to make do.
Can you thank for yourself?
Oh, yeah, thanks.
No need to worry.
Who said you fear can eat my snack?
You should cut her head, quickly!
That was close.
Carrot, you got a death grip.
Man, you're tough. Take
it. It's fine. Enjoy.
She almost took out Luffy.
she is known for being a strong
fighter whoa where did you
get up there pedro i suppose cats
do like their heights man i'm
hungry it's chow time somebody
go make us some grog i guess this
is up to me then can you keep an
eye on the water for me yes ma
'am okay it's five thousand
berries per head
you want
to eat
right Brooke maybe one of us should
step up good thinking we can't
possibly let Luffy handle this it
would surely be a death sentence
fine I'll cook you can leave
it to me I got this just watch
Oh dear, please reconsider!
Food, food, food!
Let's not be rash!
Bloopie, can you even use the stove?
Wow, quite the headline today.
The long-rumored mystery island
has finally been uncovered.
The Revolutionary Army's
headquarters, Baltigo,
has been completely devastated?
The revolutionaries got
beaten? Take a look.
Dragon's your father, is he not?
Sabo!
It's a picture of my big brother!
Huh?
That's Sabo?
I don't know all the details, but he's
the one you ran into in Dressrosa, right?
Wait, your brother is the chief of staff?
That's the second in command
in the Revolutionary Army.
You didn't mention that.
What kind of family are you?
That dragon guy beside him here.
Yes, that's your father.
You remember what your grandpa
said two years ago, right?
The name of your father is Monkey D.
Dragon, the Revolutionary.
Don't you remember anything?
That man's your father, Luffy.
That's my dad, this guy!
You just realized?
I've never seen him.
Luffy's dad is the boss of the
Revolutionary Army? So cool! So cool!
That you...
Really?
You never bothered to look him
up after you found out the truth?
You weren't even curious?
Your father's so famous, though.
Robin even said he took her
under his wing for a while.
First time seeing him.
That's really weird.
Dad sure doesn't look like me.
Anyway, I hope Sabo's okay. Wow.
Well, maybe he'd care
if he met him in person?
It says an anonymous tip led
to the discovery of their HQ.
However, by the time the
Navian Cipher pole had arrived,
the Blackbeard Pirates had brought the
location to utter ruin before fleeing
blackbeard that bastard
i know i wonder what
provoked him to attack the revolutionaries
it seems strange he could
has anything to do with
sabo he fought that
champion back in dress rosa
Sounds like Blackbeard fled After
briefly butting heads with Cypherpoll
Hey, come on, listen to
me, Luffy Fortunately,
there's no mention of
casualties in the article Hey
If your brother or father
had been killed in the
fight Their deaths would
have at least made headlines,
so I wouldn't worry Hey,
Luffy At least Ugarra can take solace
in that Oh, yeah, that's a good point.
Listen, Luffy!
What is it, Chopper? Finally!
Thanks for cooking and everything,
but is that smoke normal?
Hmm?
What smoke?
Oh, crap!
I left the stove on to die!
No!
Something exploded!
Put out the fire!
Wait a sec, there's a storm coming! What?
What's that thing?
Is it a retro?
For all the fails, the wind
will rip them to shreds!
What about the fire, though?
Don't you worry, the rain's gonna help!
Lucky us, this is your fault!
You can give us a hand, too!
I'm family wounded!
Remember all!
Carrot went out to sea
with the Straw Hats?
Why didn't Yutia tell us sooner, Baratie?
I apologize, Wanda.
I really should have said something so
someone could have talked her out of it.
Sorry.
But she told me.
No way.
If anybody finds out, they'll stop me.
Uh-huh.
Did she pay Yutia off?
All right, all right, I've been caught.
Believe me when I say Carrot
didn't want to betray you, Karoo.
That's fine.
I'm just glad to know where she is.
I was more worried about
her being missing in action.
If she's with Luffy, she'll be safe.
Everything's okay.
Please take your rest now, Duke.
We'll have extra guards on duty.
I have suspicions that the
enemy possesses a Vivre card.
I can't help but wonder
how they obtained one.
I only hope the card was lost along
with the fleet that Zunesha sank.
You do think they'll return?
I believe we should stay vigilant.
Agreed.
Come on...
You'll pull me out of here already!
Commander Kaido!
Master Jack failed to rescue Joker!
What should we do?
Do you realize that puts our
arrangements for our smile tree?
Six feet under, Commander!
He's an emotional drunk today.
Then that means we won't be
able to create any more gifters.
Joking!
Why joking?
How could you let yourself
get beaten like that?
You promised we'd make
the greatest crew ever.
It'd be filled with pirates
with Devil Fruit powers.
And yet...
Before our dream could come true...
You got your ass handed to you
by a couple of piss-pant brats.
Damn Joker, you dumb bastard!
This is all because you
were such a weakling!
I don't know, sir.
This Straw Hat guy seems pretty tough.
You were saying.
Go on then!
Who do you think I am?
He's an angry drunk!
Come on, Commander Kaku.
There's no need to lose your cool.
Straw Hat Luffy and Trafalgar Law.
Let me take a guess.
They're Worst Generation Trash.
They must think they're really
something taking down a Warlord.
But they've messed with my business,
and now they'll pay for it in blood.
Enough with those brats.
Wake up, boy.
Listen closely.
Warn your little playmates.
Run while you can.
Playing pirate is going to get
you and everyone you love killed.
Eustass Captain Kent.
It's chilly.
The roof is patched up.
Great, nice work.
All right, the storm has passed
and the ship is repaired.
Plus, I saved the food. Don't be shy.
Let's dig in.
Yay, we get to eat.
We're all so hungry.
Isn't that good?
It's my signature curry.
Lucy, we can't eat rice
that hasn't been cooked.
What exactly is that bitter purple duck?
There's so many bones in this.
And so much jam, too.
That blue sludge won't release my spoon.
What did I ever do to you to deserve this?
I went to a lot of
trouble to whip this up.
You guys are being rude.
We can't eat this crap!
We're going to spill it!
Sanji would be furious to find out
you're wasting what's technically food.
What happened?
We had this place stocked with provisions.
Well, I kept on screwing things
up, so I used everything. What?
There was nearly a weak
supply of food for us.
I thought you were hungry.
This isn't a joke!
What are we supposed to do now?
Oh, Lucy?
We're gonna die of starvation.
And so, on the first
day of Luffy's voyage,
the group is already waging a
battle against malnutrition.
I thought it was snow, but...
It is le cotton candy fleury.
The transponderous nail's
been ringing off the hook.
Is this a warning signal?
No, meaning we have already entered
the territory of the moment.
And it's broadcasting
over there, I take it?
Oui, monsieur.
As Le Snow says, this is Star 28.
It is an avant-post where a platoon of the
Big Mom pirates is
standing at l 'attention.
If this was not airship, we would suffer.
Les bombes, enfants, tragiques.
Now, I do hope you have
decided to be less stubborn.
And join notre Family.
Though it's not just the big mom pirates!
You would also be swearing allegiance
to the mighty German W6, n 'est-ce pas?
Then no one gets out and
your dear papa is happy
You think I give a crap
what that bastard wants?
I never want to see him again.
He makes me sick.
I only came to bring this to a close.
No need to be so antagonistic.
Mama is rather looking
forward to this arrangement.
Of course she is aware that you are some
colleague of that imbecile Straw Hat.
But she thinks very highly
of you for your work at un
restaurant celebre in Lisbleu
where you were trained so well.
Mama may give you a highly desirable
position if you can cook well enough.
Yeah, screw that!
These hands have one job only.
And that's cooking for my crewmates
as long as they'll have me.
I went through hell itself to
become a better chef. All for them.
In fact, I bet they're missing
my cooking as we speak.
Stomachs growling with
tears in their eyes.
Ridiculous.
You guys wouldn't understand.
You stabbed one of your own crewmates
in the back and didn't even care.
Punks like that aren't worthy of my food.
Oh, talking about Pec Homes,
we let business get personal.
B .G.
did the right thing.
Baron Tamago.
Vito!
We got a photo, Lili, of Lady Pudding
from Whole Cake Island for you to see.
Well,
it's not perfect, but I know you're
kind of iffy about this whole deal,
so at least you won't be going in blind
when you meet your betrothed, Lili.
There's not gonna be a wedding, jackass.
What difference does a photo make?
Just take a look.
You want me to kick you to death or what?
Oh, don't be cruel, Lelon.
Get off my ass!
Uh-oh.
This is your fiancée, Lelon.
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte
family, Lady Charlotte Pudding.
Thank you.